

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- 3D Studio Max / Mentalray (10 years)
- V-ray (5 years)
- Vectorworks (10 years)
- Sketchup (5 years)
- Adobe Creative Suite (10 years)
- HTML (1 year)
- CSS (1 year)
- Javascript (In Progress)
- Wordpress (3 years)

LET'S CHAT:

617-898-8070 16 Nelson Dr Apt 1A. Randolph, MA 02368

Email: htexhibitdesign@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://htranboston.github.io/

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/huy-tran-1b309644

REFERENCES:

Available upon request

Huy M. Tran

M. Arch | Experience Designer | Front-end Developer

HERE'S MY STORY

I'm an exhibit designer with more than 10 years of experience in the exhibit and trade show industry. Some people call it environmental design; others call it experimental design. I often describe my role as a brand promoter. Throughout my career, I use architectural design principles to promote brand experience through forms and spaces. Currently, I am looking to expand my design capability from the physical world into the digital world.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern Architect

ZGF ARCHITECTS LLP - PORTLAND, OR SUMMER 2007

- Create 3D models of buildings and furniture
- Assist architects with 3D rendering and visualization
- Create textures for use in 3D rendering

CAD Drafter

UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO - MOSCOW, ID 2008-2009

- Maintain and edit blueprints of various buildings on campus.
- Archive old blueprints

Teaching Assistant

UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO - MOSCOW, ID 2008-2009

- Critique second year design students' projects
- Give tutorials on Photoshop, Illustrator and 3D Studio Max

Senior Exhibit Designer

THE EXHIBIT SOURCE - WESTWOOD, MA 2010-PRESENT

- Develop concepts and prepare preliminary drawings of permanent and temporary exhibits, office interiors and environments
- Provide detailed construction drawings, material specifications and setup drawings.

EDUCATIONAL INFO

University of Idaho - Moscow, ID

M.ARCH MASTER IN ARCHITECTURE FOCUS ON MODULAR DESIGN

- Graduated Class of 2009 with a 4.0 GPA
- Winner of Juan & Sean De Leon Leadership Award
- Winner of Lloyd E. Stalker (Architecture Excellent Award)
- Winner of Hayes, Walter C. Engineering Scholarship

Manchester Christian Academy - Manchester, WA

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

- Graduated Class of 2004 Valedictorian